<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kmymoney.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KMyMoney</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKMyMoneyxx</name>
  <summary>Personal Finance Manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Osobní správce financí</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Styring af privatøkonomi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Persönliche Finanzenverwaltung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Személyes pénzügyi kezelő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Persoonlijk financieel beheer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie finansami osobistymi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gestor de Finanças Pessoais</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de Finanças Pessoais</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Osobný manažér financií</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Hemekonomihanterare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для керування особистими фінансами</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPersonal Finance Managerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KMyMoney is a personal finance manager for KDE.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="da">KMyMoney er styring af privatøkonomien til KDE</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KMyMoney ist eine persönliche Finanzverwaltung für KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KMyMoney egy személyes pénzügyi kezelő KDE felülethez.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KMyMoney is een persoonlijke financieelbeheerder voor KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KMyMoney służy do zarządzania finansami osobistymi w KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KMyMoney é um gestor de finanças pessoais para o KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KMyMoney é um gerenciador de finanças pessoais para o KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KMyMoney je osobný správca financií pre KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KMyMoney är en hemekonomihanterare för KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KMyMoney — програма для керування особистими фінансами для KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKMyMoney is a personal finance manager for KDE.xx</p>
    <p>
      It supports different account types, categorisation of expenses and incomes, reconciliation of bank accounts and import/export to the “QIF” file format.
      Direct download using the OFX and HBCI formats is also possible via plugins.
      Online banking support (statement download) is also provided for the OFX and HBCI protocols.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Den understøtter forskellige kontotyper, kategorisering af udgifter og indtægter, afstemning af bankkonti og import/eksport af filformatet "QIF". Direkte download med brug af af formaterne OFX og HBCI er også muligt via plugins. Netbankunderstøttelse (download af kontoudtog) leveres også for protokollerne OFX og HBCI.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het ondersteunt verschillende typen rekeningen, in categorieën indelen van uitgaven en inkomsten, controle op bankrekeningen en importeren/exporteren naar het “QIF” bestandsformaat. Direct downloaden met de OFX en HBCI formaten is ook mogelijk via plug-ins. Onderstuening voor online bankieren (downloaden van afschriften) wordt ook geleverd voor de OFX en HBCI protocollen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Obsługuje różne rodzaj kont, kategoryzacje rozchodów i przychodów, uzgadnianie kont bankowych oraz importowanie/eksportowanie do formatu plików “QIF”. Bezpośrednie pobieranie przy użyciu formatów OFX oraz HBCI również jest możliwe poprzez wtyczki. Obsługa bankowości w sieci (pobieranie wyciągów) jest również zapewniona przez protokoły OFX oraz HBCI.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Suporta diferentes tipos de contas, a classificação de despesas e receitas, a consolidação das contas dos bancos e a importação/exportação para o formato de ficheiros "QIF". Também é possível a transferência directa dos formatos OFX e HBCI, através de 'plugins'. O suporte para a banca 'online' (com a transferência de extractos) também está disponível para os protocolos OFX e HBCI.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Tem suporte a diferentes tipos de contas, a classificação de despesas e receitas por categoria, a conciliação das contas bancárias e a importação/exportação para o formato de arquivos "QIF". Por meio de plugins, também é possível baixar diretamente usando os formatos OFX e HBCI. Também há suporte para banco online (baixar extratos) através dos protocolos OFX e HBCI.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Podporuje rôzne typy účtov, kategorizáciu výdavkov a príjmov, súlad bankových účtov a import/export do formátu "QIF". Priame sťahovanie pomocou formátov OFX a HBCI je možné cez pluginy. Podpora online bankingu je možná pre protokoly OFX a HBCI.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Den stöder olika kontotyper, kategorisering av utgifter och inkomster, avstämning av bankkonton samt import från och export till filformatet "QIF". Direkt nerladdning med användning av formaten OFX och HBCI är också möjlig via insticksprogram. Stöd för internetbank (nerladdning av kontoutdrag) tillhandahålls också för protokollen OFX och HBCI.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У програмі передбачено різні типи рахунків, категоризацію за витратами та надходженнями коштів, звірення банківських рахунків, а також імпортування та експортування даних у форматі QIF. Крім того, можливе безпосереднє отримання банківських даних (виписок) з інтернету у форматах OFX та HBCI за допомогою додатків.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt supports different account types, categorisation of expenses and incomes, reconciliation of bank accounts and import/export to the “QIF” file format. Direct download using the OFX and HBCI formats is also possible via plugins. Online banking support (statement download) is also provided for the OFX and HBCI protocols.xx</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>KMyMoney has a welcome page to help new users get off to a good start.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">KMyMoney har en velkomstside til at hjælpe nye brugere godt i gang.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">KMyMoney heeft een welkomstpagina om nieuwe gebruikers bij een goede start te helpen.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">KMyMoney zawiera stronę powitalną, aby pomoc nowym użytkownikom w szybkim rozpoczęciu pracy.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">O KMyMoney tem uma página de boas-vindas para ajudar os utilizadores novos a terem um bom início.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">O KMyMoney tem uma página de boas-vindas para ajudar os novos usuários a terem um bom começo.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">KMyMoney má uvítaciu stránku na pomoc novým používateľom na dobrý začiatok.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">KMyMoney har en välkomstsida för att hjälpa nya användare att komma igång.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">У KMyMoney передбачено сторінку вітання, за допомогою якої новим користувачам буде простіше розпочати користування програмою.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxKMyMoney has a welcome page to help new users get off to a good start.xx</caption>
      <image>http://www.kmymoney.org/images/screenshots/large/kmm1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The financial summary gives you an overview of your finances, including overdue and upcoming scheduled transactions.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Økonomioversigten giver dig en oversigt over din økonomi, derunder forfaldne og kommende planlagte transaktioner.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">De financiële samenvatting geeft u een overzicht van uw financiën, inclusief over de rand en aankomende geplande transacties.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Podsumowanie finansowe daje pogląd na twoje finanse, uwzględniając transakcje po terminie i te zaplanowane.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">O resumo financeiro dá-lhe uma visão geral sobre as suas finanças, incluindo as transacções atrasadas e agendadas para breve.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">O resumo financeiro lhe apresenta uma visão geral das suas finanças, incluindo as transações vencidas e agendadas.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Finančný sumár vám poskytne prehľad vašich financií, vrátane neuhradených a blížiacich sa naplánovaných transakcií.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Den ekonomiska sammanfattningen ger en översikt av ekonomin, inklusive försenade och kommande planerade transaktioner.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">За допомогою сторінки фінансового резюме вам буде простіше розібратися з поточним фінансовим станом. На цій сторінці буде показано також прострочені та наступні заплановані фінансові операції.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxThe financial summary gives you an overview of your finances, including overdue and upcoming scheduled transactions.xx</caption>
      <image>http://www.kmymoney.org/images/screenshots/large/kmm2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>In this view your accounts are organized, viewed, and managed by the institutions they are held at.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">I denne visning er dine regnskaber organiseret, fremvist og håndteret af de institutioner de hører til.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">In deze weergave zijn uw rekeningen georganiseerd, getoond en beheerd door de banken waar ze berusten.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">W tym widoku konta są urządzane, oglądane i zarządzane przez instytucje, w których się je obsługuje.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Nesta janela, poderá organizar, ver e gerir as suas contas, com base nas instituições em que estas estão guardadas.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Nesta janela as suas contas podem ser organizadas, visualizadas e gerenciadas, com base nas instituições em que estão guardadas.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">V tomto pohľade sú vaše účty usporiadané, zobrazené a spravované inštitúciami, ktoré ich držia.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">I den här vyn organiseras, granskas och hanteras konton enligt institution som de hör till.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Рахунки на сторінці резюме упорядковано за установами, з якими ці рахунки пов’язано.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxIn this view your accounts are organized, viewed, and managed by the institutions they are held at.xx</caption>
      <image>http://www.kmymoney.org/images/screenshots/large/kmm3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.kmymoney.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=kmymoney4&amp;format=guided</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/extragear-office/kmymoney/index.html</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmymoney</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
